

## **Tamlica Muhaimin**

Fullstack Engineer

- O D.I. Yogyakarta
- **&** 6285275737705
- @ tamlicamuhaimin@outlook.com

## Skills

## **Python**

Javascript

**NodeJS** 

ReactJS

# Typescript

#### Certifications

# Certified Entry-Level Python Programmer (PCEP-30-02)

Python Institute

June 2024

https://verify.openedg.org/

Credential ID: oMad.ZRs1.BxWQ

## Web Developer

Badan Nasional Sertifikasi Profesi (BNSP)

December 2022

Credential ID:

620102513600354822022

## **Awards**

## Speaker

INFINITE x GDSC UNY

March 2024

## Languages

**English** 

## Bahasa Indonesia

#### **Profiles**

## in Tamlica Muhaimin

## Tamlica M.

## Summary

I have experience in developing websites and web app with various frameworks such as VueJS, NuxtJS, Django, Laravel, and Golang. I am familiar with REST API and I also have experience in using RDBMS databases or noSQL database such as MySQL, PostgreSQL, and MongoDB. I prefer to use the Python programming language, but, I also interested to learn the best programming language on their own and required field.

## Experience

#### T'Lab

September 2021 - Present

Yogyakarta

Full Stack Engineer

https://tlab.co.id/

- · Building backends for mobile and web applications in Django
- Building frontend applications using VueJS
- Developing local bank monitoring system for foreign exchange transactions against rupiah directly and realtime
- Adding new functionalities to an existing Web Application (Django, HTML, JS, CSS)
- · Maintaining and fixing bugs for various Web Applications
- Database (PostgreSQL, MongoDB, ElasticSearch)
- Creating Python script (Unit Testing, Bot, Web Scrapping)
- Version control system (Git, Github, GitLab)

## Projek.do

September 2020 - September 2022

Head Programmer / Owner

Banda Aceh

- https://www.instagram.com/projek.do/
- Developing an online flight and hotel booking website (Laravel)
- Building backends for coffee shop mobile applications (Laravel, PHP)
- Building microcontroller projects using Arduino
- Create an IoT microcontroller projects that synchronises device and mobile applications (Arduino, Wemos, BLYNK app, Telegram Bot)

#### Education

## Universitas Teknologi Bandung (UTB)

Information Technology

2022 - Present

Bachelor Degree

Politeknik Aceh

2017 - 2020

Mechatronics

3.65

Associate Degree